[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This aromatic perennial herb, that is native to Europe, North Africa and Asia, is widely used in many cuisines, especially in the Mediterranean.", "correct_answer": "Thyme", "incorrect_answers": ["Poppy", "Pepper", "Paprika"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stilton is a cheese which originated in which country?", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "The Netherlands", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which director, known as the father of Bond films, directed the motion picture, Dr. No?", "correct_answer": "Terence Young", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Fleisher", "Anthony Mann", "Don Siegel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?", "correct_answer": "Abu Dhabi", "incorrect_answers": ["Al Riyadh", "Dauha", "Dubai"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There was a sequel to the movie The Blair Witch Project.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This doctor takes care of you and your baby during pregnancy.", "correct_answer": "Obstetrician", "incorrect_answers": ["Psychologist", "Periodontist", "Pediatrician"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In August 2002 actor Jon Voight claimed this about his daughter Angelina Jolie on Access Hollywood.", "correct_answer": "He said she was having serious mental problems.", "incorrect_answers": ["He swore he didnt want to see her children ever.", "He confessed she was everything to him and wishes to have her by his side all the time.", "He said no man will ever be good enough for his little girl."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the number of neutrons in the nucleus of an atom determine?", "correct_answer": "The isotope of the element", "incorrect_answers": ["The bonds the element forms", "The charge of the ions of the element", "The element itself"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Johnnys real last name in the movie Johnny Dangerously?", "correct_answer": "Kelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Jones", "Corleone", "Alto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which tree, that grows on the Canary Islands, Cape Verde and Madeira, secretes a reddish juice, called Dragons blood?", "correct_answer": "Dracaena draco", "incorrect_answers": ["Para rubber tree", "The Canary Island Pine", "Castanopsis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Stegasaurus had a second brain in its back.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US, all Medicare Part A participants pay a premium for the service.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]